https://www.perkinelmer.com/corporate/policies/

Cookies on PerkinElmer
PerkinElmer uses cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience possible on our website. This may include cookies from third party websites. If you continue without changing your settings, we will assume that you consent to receive cookies from this website. You can change your cookie settings at any time. To learn more, please review our cookie policy, which includes information on how to manage your cookies.
Continue
Home
All Policies
All Policies
All Policies
All Policies
Privacy Policy
Website Terms & Conditions
Terms & Conditions of Sale
Terms & Conditions of Sale - Life Sciences Reagents
Terms & Conditions of Service
HR Personal Data Protection
Supplier Information
Cookie Policy
PerkinElmer respects your privacy. We want to make use of personal identification information that you provide to us for purposes of serving you better. "Personal identification information" is information that lets us identify you, such as your email address, name and address. PerkinElmer uses the personal identification information to selectively send you communications that may be of interest to you. For any questions on personal data and privacy, please send an email to personaldata@perkinelmer.com.
Updated on
March 30, 2018
This Web site is provided by PerkinElmer, Inc., and its affiliate companies and subsidiaries (hereinafter, "PerkinElmer") and is provided for informational purposes only. By using this site or downloading materials from this site, you agree to these terms and conditions. If you do not agree to be bound by these terms and conditions, please do not use this site or download materials from this site.
Updated on
October 31, 2014
PerkinElmer's Terms & Conditions of Sale shall govern all orders for and purchases of products as well as installation of equipment.
Updated on
July 11, 2019
PerkinElmer's Terms & Conditions of Sale for Life Sciences Reagents shall govern all orders for and purchases of reagents products relevant to the Life Sciences Reagent Business.
Updated on
October 01, 2020
PerkinElmer's Terms & Conditions of Service shall govern orders for core instrument service provided by PerkinElmer to our customers, including PerkinElmer service plans and billable services.
Updated on
July 11, 2019
In compliance with the United Kingdom ("UK") Finance Act 2016, Schedule 19, paragraph 19, this UK Tax Strategy Statement sets out the approach of PerkinElmer, Inc.
Updated on
January 08, 2019
PerkinElmer is committed to protecting any personally identifiable information (i.e., any information by which you can be identified) that you provide to us. We have prepared this Online Privacy Statement to refer you to our Privacy Policy and to explain how you can make the choices about the way your information is collected and used.
Updated on
March 30, 2018
PerkinElmer is a customer driven organization that strives to meet or exceed its customers' expectations in respect to product performance, quality, value and timeliness of services. As a direct extension of this commitment, PerkinElmer's selection of and expectations for its suppliers, requires a like commitment from our suppliers.
Updated on
October 12, 2017
PerkinElmer uses cookies in order to enhance your experience on our website and ensure that our website functions.You can visit this page at any time to learn more about cookies, get the most up to date information on how we use cookies and manage your cookie settings. We will not use cookies for any purpose other than the ones stated, but please note that we reserve the right to update our cookies.
Updated on
March 30, 2018
This statement has been prepared by the Trustee of the PerkinElmer UK Money Purchase Pension Scheme (the “Scheme”) to demonstrate how the Scheme has complied with the governance standards introduced under The Occupational Pension Plans (Charges and Governance) Regulations 2015.
Déclarée grande cause nationale du quinquennat par le président de la République Française, l’égalité professionnelle entre les femmes et les hommes passe par une mobilisation de tous. La Loi pour la Liberté de choisir son avenir professionnel soumet les entreprises à une obligation de résultat. Elle a créé l’Index de l’égalité salariale FemmesHommes. Il est calculé chaque année à partir de 4 ou 5 indicateurs selon la taille de l’entreprise : rémunérations, augmentations, promotions, congés maternité, parité du top management. Il doit être rendu public et transmis à l’inspection du travail.L’index 2019 pour la PerkinElmer SAS en France est de 62 points sur 100. Les indicateurs indiquent pour 2019 des niveaux de rémunération plus favorables envers les femmes et, à contrario, plus favorables envers les hommes en matière d’augmentation de salaire. La parité est atteinte en ce qui concerne la parité du top management. PerkinElmer SAS continue à mettre en place en 2020 des actions visant à réduire les écarts de rémunération entre les hommes et les femmes et à garantir l’égalité entre les Femmes et les Hommes en matière de travail.
NOTICE: You are now leaving the PerkinElmer website.
The privacy policy of the site to which you are going may differ from PerkinElmer's privacy policy. To remain at the PerkinElmer site and return to your previous page, click the button Cancel.
To leave the PerkinElmer site for the link you selected, click the button OK.
OK
Cancel
